module.exports = {
    trivia: [
        /* BOILERPLATE
		{
			question: "",
			answers: ["[]", "[]", "[]", "[]"],
			correct: ,
		},
        */
        {
            question: "What is the name of Jaiden's younger brother?",
            answers: ["James", "Jax", "Jimmy", "Jerry"],
            correct: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "For which channel has Jaiden animated before?",
            answers: ["Zoella", "IHasCupquake", "Ninja", "Shane Dawson"],
            correct: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "What race was Keisha",
            answers: ["Collie", "Golden Retriever", "German Sheperd", "Shetland Sheepdog"],
            correct: 0,
        },
        {
            question: "Is Jaiden allergic to cats?",
            answers: ["Yes", "No"],
            correct: 0,
        },
        {
            question: "Jaiden has the same birthday as which other animator?",
            answers: ["TheOdd1sOut", "IHasCupquake", "Domics", "SomeThingElseYT"],
            correct: 2,
        },
        {
            question: "What is Jaiden's Mom and Dad's eye color",
            answers: ["Brown, Hazel", "Hazel, Brown", "Blue, Hazel", "Hazel, Blue"],
            correct: 0,
        },
        {
            question: "Quote: Wow, I'm such a freaking adult",
            answers: ["How to be Stupid", "Random Thoughts", "I'm too Awkward for My Own Good", "Things that Happened While I Grew up"],
            correct: 3,
        },
        {
            question: "Upload date of 'Things that Happened While I Grew up'",
            answers: ["June 10 2018", "September 10 2018", "October 15 2018", "August 15 2018"],
            correct: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "Expert: Meaning of 'The most superlative objects come from hacked nourishment'",
            answers: ["Best things comes from sliced bread", "With a piece of bread you can find paradise under a palm tree", "There is not a thing more positive than bread", "Without bread, all is misery"],
            correct: 0,
        },
        {
            question: "Expert: Meaning of 'Hoopla blabs more rambunctious than discussion.'",
            answers: ["They way to get started is to quit talking and begin doing", "Tell me and I forget. Teach me and I remember. Involve me and I learn", "Actions speak louder than words"],
            correct: 2,
        },
        {
            question: "'I totally get an A++ Super with stars and hearts and the persons little avatar would go'",
            answers: ["finger guns", "SUGOI", "dabbing"],
            correct: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "A kitchen ornament with nothing but a funny looking rooster on it and in bold letters the word",
            answers: ["SEAT", "EAT", "DRINK", "COFFEE"],
            correct: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "Hard: 'Even though I enjoy good decor I also...'",
            answers: ["love candles.", "bought this stuffed toucan and he makes me very happy.", "want it to stay as homemade.", "don't take it very seriously."],
            correct: 3,
        },
        {
            question: "Hard: Quote: 'Wonder if I can copyright it too'",
            answers: ["Things I Do that Adults Probably Don't Do", "I'm too Awkward for My Own Good", "Random Thoughts", "How to Make Life More Interesting"],
            correct: 0,
        },
        {
            question: "Quote: 'I think I\'m supposed to fall in the category of adult now'",
            answers: ["Parent Stories", "Random Thoughts", "Things I Do that Adults Probably Don't Do", "My Childhood Stories"],
            correct: 2,
        },
		/*{
		  	question: "Quote: 'Two can play at that game James'",
		  	answers: ["[]", "[]", "[]", "Things I Do that Adults Probably Don't Do"],
		  	correct: 3,
		},*/
		{
			question: "Will you hold something for me?",
			answers: ["My Wallet", "My Hand", "Ari", "My Card"],
			correct: 1,
		},
		{
			question: "Don't feed wild ducks bread, give them...",
			answers: ["Candy Bars", "Half Popped Popcorn", "Donuts", "Chips"],
			correct: 0,
		},
        {
			question: "Quote: 'Jaiden you\'re so good all of the time, you gotta be rebellious every once in a while'",
			answers: ["The History of my Hair", "Our tour went wrong in all the best ways", "Childhood Stories", "I Attempted a Speedrun (and got a world record)"],
			correct: 2,
		},
        {
			question: "She had to crack the door open and say...",
			answers: ["I'm counting to 3!", "Any longer?", "Calmed down?", "Are you done?"],
			correct: 3,
		},
        /*{
			question: "Quote: 'What do you think you did?'",
			answers: ["[]", "Childhood stories", "[]", "[]"],
			correct: 1,
		},*/
        {
			question: "What did Jaiden do when her mom said 'What do you think you did?'",
			answers: ["Played outside with pyjamas", "Walked Kaisha without telling anyone", "Ate the whole bag of chips", "Stole mom's candy"],
			correct: 0,
		},
        {
			question: "What mountain did Jaiden fail to date in",
			answers: ["A Mountain", "Englihtenment Mountain", "Mount Rushmore", "Four Peaks"],
			correct: 0,
		},
        {
			question: "What kind of bird is Ari?",
			answers: ["Maroon-Bellied Conure", "Green Cheek Conure", "Blaze-Winged Parakeet", "Black-Capped Conure"],
			correct: 1,
		},
        {
			question: "What video is Ari's first appearance in the channel?",
			answers: ["Parent Stories", "Cringing at My Old Drawings (100k Milestone)", "My Childhood Obsession with Animals", "New Member of the Family!"],
			correct: 3,
		},
        {
			question: "When was Tofu first teased?",
			answers: ["The Most Underrated Game", "New Member of the Family!", "Cringing at My Old Drawings (100k Milestone)", "My Dog Stories"],
			correct: 0,
		},
        {
			question: "What is Jaiden's favorite color?",
			answers: ["Pink", "Blue", "Purple", "Green"],
			correct: 0,
		},
        {
			question: "Expert: When is Jaiden's birthday?",
			answers: ["September 14, 1994", "September 27, 1994", "September 14, 1997", "September 27, 1997"],
			correct: 3,
		},	 
        {
			question: "What is a super long 3 pronged sharp fork?",
			answers: ["A Lawn Trimmer", "A Knife", "A Trident"],
			correct: 2,
		},	
        {
			question: "What game was in \â€œthe most underrated game\"",
			answers: ["The Powerpuff Girls: Battle HIM", "SpongeBob Battle For Bikini Bottom", "Fossil Fighters"],
			correct: 2,
		},
	]
};
